[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 19]
Yao, sleep early.
Granny, don't worry about me.
Go to sleep.
Help!
Spider, don't come here.
Don't come here.
Go over there.
Don't come over here.
Don't come...
Don't.
Brother.
Don't come over here.
Go aside.
Hu, what's wrong?
Big grasshopper.
Don't come over.
You...
Back off.
You... You've drunk too much.
Don't come over.
Hu.
Damai.
Don't come over.
What's wrong, Damai?
The snake and grasshopper are together.
Hongdou!
Hongdou, get some help!
Nana, what's wrong?
Don't cry.
I'll be right over.
Quack.
Every year, many families are carried in.
If they're lucky,
they get stomach and intestinal bleeding,
and walk out on their own when they get well.
If they are unlucky,
they will be carried out
in the way of being carried in.
Dare to eat the unfamiliar
wild mushrooms on the mountain.
How many lives do people have?
Yes.
Must pay attention in the future.
With this lesson,
they may not dare to eat mushrooms
in the near future.
Sorry to bother you so late.
Thank you for your hard work.
Quack.
Hu.
What are you looking for?
There are frogs on their beds.
Lie down quickly.
Don't touch me, dirty.
Nana,
go back to rest.
I'll keep an eye on it here.
It's dawn now.
Xiaochun will come over.
It doesn't matter.
I'm just worried about them.
Their symptoms are mild.
Every year there are a few cases.
It's normal.
I won't dare to eat mushrooms.
You won't.
You'll forget in a few days.
[Dali City, Luoxia Town Health Center]
How is Hongdou?
She sweated so much,
she must feel uncomfortable.
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
Everyone,
I'm back.
Hu.
Damai.
Dou.
Hei.
I'm asking you, where are they?
You only know eating.
Mushrooms.
I fried them with ham last night.
I know them all.
I didn't see any poisonous ones.
Then the lurid bolete was undercooked.
No wonder.
Luckily, it's not serious.
How is it?
They are fine.
They've gone back to rest.
Luckily, they're fine.
Otherwise, how would you
explain to their father, right?
Yes.
Is there not enough
staff in the cafe today?
Yes.
Chuchu and Granny Caiyun have gone to Xiaguan
for old granny's birthday.
She asked me to cover for her.
There are Hongdou
and Nana in the cafe.
I think we have enough staff.
This accident makes it worse.
Is Hongdou going
back in a while?
You need to recruit
people for your cafe,
otherwise, it won't work.
Yes.
Our service has to keep up.
As soon as the rain stopped,
our Zeqing went to the mountains
to pick mushrooms,
and rolled a body of mud.
The mushrooms are
accepted by all the restaurants outside.
If I sell them to restaurants,
I can earn money.
They did not cook the
mushrooms themselves,
and got poisoned.
So I should not be blamed, right?
Aunt Gui, don't
take it personally.
It's just an accident.
I know.
I won't take it personally.
I didn't do the poisoning.
Yes.
But they've just been poisoned,
so their stomachs are weak.
Fish soup with tofu
and millet congee
are the best antidotes.
Oh, no!
Put it down.
It can't be eaten.
This plate has been cut with mushrooms,
and not washed well,
which can also cause poisoning.
It's not that serious.
Aunt Gui, no one
really blames you.
I know.
It should be washed clean.
Now I'm relieved.
Mr. Ma.
You went back this time.
How are your parents?
Thanks to your blessing, they're fine.
Did you tell them about your business?
What?
You...
Say it again.
I still want to start my own business.
But it's not the same as before,
I want to do industry.
Told us earlier.
God bless.
Mom and Dad,
I'm a little confused
by your attitude.
Damned Ma,
I told you that I
gave birth to my son,
I know him clearly.
He's at Xie Zhiyao's
house holding a big move.
Why can't you sleep at night,
tossing, turning and sighing?
I was scared by you.
I didn't scare you.
It was Ma who scared me.
Dad,
why did you say that?
Why did you panic?
Two days ago, when you came home,
as soon as you entered the door,
some words were written on your face,
something is wrong.
After you put down your things,
you did the laundry,
cooked, mopped the floor,
and cleaned the windows.
You cleaned everything
inside and out.
It's not worth mentioning.
I'm just doing my filial duty.
Your filial piety
scared us to death.
We've been afraid
to breathe these days.
Your father said,
it's obvious that
you've decided to become a monk,
and now you're back to inform us.
Just tell us that you
want to start a business.
It's not a big deal.
Your father and I
are not afraid that you will fail,
but that you will be beaten down,
and never recover.
You sit in the sun
with your legs crossed every day,
which scares us.
Put your legs down.
Put them down.
We're eating.
We don't want to smell your stinky feet.
I've been a vegetarian lately.
It's not stinky.
Eat the food.
It's getting cold.
Tell us more about
your business project.
Okay.
Let me tell you about it.
Look, I'm right.
Parents all over the
world feel the same way,
not afraid of children tossed,
but like a puddle of
mud which is hopeless.
Aunt Gui,
you're truly an expert.
Don't praise me.
Peel the garlic.
Okay.
Slowly. Watch the threshold.
I'm not that weak.
You're weak.
You're almost on the floor.
Come on.
Slowly.
Slow down.
These days, be
careful with your diet.
Breaking your
stomach is serious.
Put this on.
I'm not that serious.
Put it on.
Do as you're told.
Don't eat recklessly in the future.
Look,
this is cooked by Aunt Gui,
which is good for digestion.
Take a good rest for a few days.
You're back.
Did you get the money?
Of course.
My parents left me
the money to marry.
How did you convince them?
Before we just made a mistake.
Misunderstanding.
They always thought that
I was going to be a monk.
Then we made it clear.
I said I want to start a new business.
They were very happy.
I see.
How much money did your parents
leave for you to get married?
You're a miser who cares about this.
You're already like this.
I'm curious.
It's a small amount of money
to start a business.
But it's mainly a
token of heart, right?
I'm charging ahead,
and the back is stable.
Yes.
Don't talk about that.
Take good care of her.
I have to see Hu.
He is scratching holes
everywhere, very serious.
Thank you.
Don't be polite.
Have you noticed that
Mr. Ma is different?
Strength makes people confident.
Maybe this is what
he looked like before.
Frantic,
arrogant, and don't
care about others.
Disgusting.
Eat those things.
They are Aunt Gui's heart.
She must be feeling bad.
It's not her fault.
Did you print out all the
photos taken by Damai?
Print me a copy.
What do you need them for?
Then why did you print them out?
I'll use them.
How many birds are
there under your roof?
Some more have been hatched yesterday.
When did you make a photo wall?
Our agreement.
Well...
Just photos.
Nothing to look at.
What?
Why are there my photos?
What's in them?
This is my privacy.
Please respect.
Come on.
Taking care of us all night,
you haven't had a good rest.
Go to have a rest.
Slowly.
When you're done eating,
remember to text Ma
and ask him to clean it for you.
I know.
Bye bye.
♫ A few hidden heartbeats ♫
♫ Fill whose dream ♫
Chang,
did you go to cut barley?
Yes.
When are you going to Yang?
Just in a few days.
When I get back,
I'll bring you seafood.
Don't bring that.
We can't get used to it.
Okay, bye.
I'm bringing Zeqing some food.
Okay.
Hao.
Aunt Gui, you're here.
It's time to eat.
I'll eat as soon as I finish chopping.
Zeqing,
here's the food.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I'm coming.
Come here.
Okay.
I'm so scared of what
happened this morning.
My heart was pounding
all the way here.
It's not easy for
parents to raise a child.
If something bad happens here,
we can't even explain it.
Luckily, it's fine.
Don't think too much about it.
I tell you,
don't talk too much
when you get to Qingdao.
Don't tell Yang and Xi about this.
If they know it, they
will blame me again.
I won't say it.
Yang.
Have you eaten?
I'm not home.
I'm at the horse farm.
Bring your father some food.
We are good.
Yang, I tell you that
it rained several days ago,
the mushrooms are growing well.
They're growing in clutches.
As soon as it stopped raining,
your dad went up to the mountains,
and picked a lot of fimbriae,
and dried mushrooms.
I've fried them all for you.
I'll bring them to Xi and you.
Listen to me.
I made one more.
Take it to your
leader to have a taste.
Okay?
You say.
Why?
What?
I'm not going
with your father, right?
But you...
You've booked the flight tickets.
You can return it?
No.
I'm not unhappy. No.
Your work is important.
Your father and I
can always go there
whenever we want.
Your work is important, right?
Okay.
We won't go.
Next time.
Work hard.
Okay.
No more talking.
You go on working.
Hang up.
I'll send the mushrooms
to you two.
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
You go on working.
Hang up.
It's wired.
He doesn't let us go?
He said that the leader
asked him to go on business.
It happens every time.
The plane tickets are booked.
He's busy.
Being busy is good.
Forget it.
What about the mortgage
for such a big house?
He must be busy.
Right.
Well... Let's go next time.
Don't feel sad.
I don't.
Work is important.
What leader?
The tickets have been bought.
Negative comment.
All right.
Wired.
To be honest,
I don't want to go at all.
Even though the fields
have been contracted out,
Zeqing and I still have
serious jobs, right?
If the kids hadn't called,
and bought plane tickets,
I wouldn't have gone.
Yes.
That's right.
But that's work.
When there is a problem,
as soon as the leader asks,
you have to go on a business trip.
Yes.
That's it.
Feng,
don't go to the
courtyard this time.
When I go to Qingdao next time,
I'll let you know.
Fine, you don't have to tell me.
After a while, you
go to someone else.
Are you angry?
She is angry.
I asked you to take me to the courtyard
before you leave
to teach me how to clean.
You refused.
It made me come twice.
It's only 50 yuan a day.
I can earn that money by weaving basket
at home with my husband.
Feng,
I didn't mean to.
It's an accident.
Accident?
Feng.
Are you going to tell
me you don't care about
that 50 yuan?
I see your family in trouble,
when there is something good,
I always think of you.
Are you thinking of me,
or are you making me unhappy?
How could?
If you want to show
off, just go to show off.
My life is bad, but my family
is not as poor as you think.
You don't have to
advertise for me every day,
telling it to the people you meet.
No need.
What do you mean by that?
Nothing.
If there is nothing
else, just leave.
I'm still at work.
I'm busy.
I won't leave.
What do you mean by nothing?
Please explain it clearly.
Stop.
What's the situation?
Why are you angry?
No.
Xiaochun, what she's saying.
What is showing off?
What is publicity?
What am I promoting?
It's the truth.
What?
What am I bad for you?
Say it clearly
what you just said.
Don't be sarcastic.
Others do not know,
but we know each other very well.
When Yang failed the
college entrance exam,
you refused to let him re-read,
saying he could only
get a normal job after four more years.
You wanted him to drive
after graduating from high school.
I tried my best to persuade you.
Otherwise, your
Yang is just a driver.
And Xi, you forced
her to study accounting.
She has ignored
you for many years.
She calls me and
asks me everything.
Have you forgotten all of these?
What does 800 years ago
have to do with the present?
You're so funny.
All right.
You... You're just jealous.
You don't want others
to live better than you.
All right, Aunt Gui,
we are still working.
Don't you have to cook at home?
Go home now.
Xiaochun,
look what she's become now.
To be honest, she's
not as nice to me
as she used to be.
Yang is concerned about me,
afraid that I will be tired,
so he doesn't let me
take care of the child.
But she says that
Yang dislikes that
I can not take care of the child.
It's true.
I'm just better off than you.
You only have one son, Xie Qiang,
who is still in jail.
Don't show off here.
Don't mention Xie Qiang.
You know I don't eat mushrooms,
you still gave mushrooms to us.
Aunt Gui.
Are you crazy?
All right.
Go.
Are you crazy?
Don't eat mushrooms.
Why?
Aunt Gui really has no
control over her mouth.
She can't remember
what she said herself.
Aunt Baoping also said a lot.
Such as don't be
like that Xie Qiang
who steals and goes to jail.
Yes, every time she
says that, I blame her.
Aunt Feng is very
uncomfortable, right?
The only negative example
in their minds is Xie Qiang.
But
I think Aunt Feng is also wrong.
Aunt Gui brought her mushrooms,
but she didn't eat them and got angry.
It's your business if
you don't eat, right?
It's kind of people
to give it to you.
Aunt Gui was really
talking about the wrong thing.
What do you mean?
You know Aunt Feng had
a daughter before, right?
Of course.
I heard that some years ago
she went with her classmates
to the mountains to pick wild cherries,
and accidentally fell into the ditch.
Yes.
They went to pick wild cherries.
But Yun fell down
because she saw mushrooms there,
and wanted to pick them.
But it was raining that day,
the soil was loosened,
so she fell down.
But people in the village only knew that
she went to pick wild cherries,
no one knew it was a mushroom.
The students who went with her
told Aunt Feng's family that
she wanted to pick some mushrooms
to sell to subsidize the family.
But
Aunt Gui is so close to Aunt Feng,
does she not know about this?
Aunt Feng is strong.
She didn't say that, how
would the others know?
How do you know?
Xie Qiang told me.
Right.
You and Xie Qiang grew up together.
You take those buns out.
I'll put out the porridge.
Cooked?
It's cold outside.
You guys stay in the house.
Take a good rest these days
to nourish your stomach.
Damai, does your
stomach still hurt?
Much better.
Thank you.
Sorry to trouble you.
Don't say that.
Trouble each other
properly are friends.
No trouble at all,
that's strangers.
Right?
I'm back.
Is there any meal for me?
Yes.
Let me get you a bowl.
Come here.
Have a seat.
So hungry that my stomach is perforated.
I only ate a little cookie for lunch.
It's going too far.
When the cafe is short-staffed,
there are more customers.
So many customers today?
A group of students from
the Academy of Fine Arts
came to sketch.
They said Granny Xiuying's clothes
were beautiful, and
dragged her to be a model,
painting a whole afternoon.
Was Xiaochun not in the cafe?
I worked at the warehouse as Chuchu.
Granny Caiyun took
Chuchu to Xiaguan
for her mother's birthday.
Granny Caiyun is so old,
is her mother still alive?
96 years old.
She plays cards every day.
As long as she wins some money,
she will be very happy.
She even buys snacks for Granny Caiyun.
I tell you,
although Granny
Caiyun is 70 years old,
she has three
brothers older than her.
She is the most favored
daughter of her family.
Whenever her brothers
have anything good to eat,
they even ask their children
to bring it to Granny Caiyun.
She's so lucky.
She is 70 years old,
and still loved by her mom and brothers.
Yes.
Aunt Feng always
says that Granny Caiyun
has the best life
among all the people she's ever met.
If she was half as
lucky as Granny Caiyun,
she would burn incense
and bow down every day.
Is Aunt Feng's life bad?
Her life is too bad.
You can't say that.
Until the last moment,
we can't make such a conclusion.
Aunt Feng and Uncle
Chang are not too old,
and Xie Qiang will soon be out,
their better days are yet to come.
Out?
Is her son in prison?
Here's the thing.
Her son Xie Qiang
and brother and Guanjun
are all childhood friends.
After graduating from high school,
he didn't get into college.
And Aunt Feng told him to re-read.
But he didn't do that.
He found a temporary
job in a company
to guard the warehouse.
At that time, he met a
group of social loafers.
They drank and made trouble every day,
and called each other brothers.
These people knew that
Xie Qiang worked in the warehouse.
So they encouraged him to steal
the steel and cable in the warehouse,
and then took out
as scrap to sell.
I remember that
they were sold for
tens of thousands of yuan.
But in fact,
those are worth hundreds of thousands.
It took more than a
year to be discovered.
Too stupid.
He just went astray.
At that time, they said that
if they paid back the money,
his sentence could be reduced.
Then Aunt Feng and Uncle Chang
went from house to house
in the village to borrow money,
and owed a lot of debt.
Now the old couple
try to save money these years,
and even want to work all day long.
They not only grow
fruit trees in the fields,
but also weave baskets and tie brooms
during their free time.
They're having a hard time.
Let's not talk about this.
Eat well.
Be careful of indigestion.
These buns are good.
I made the stuffing, and Granny made it.
I need to eat more.
They're coming to sketch tomorrow.
I'm well now.
I'll go to the cafe tomorrow.
You don't have to go.
Just have a good rest.
I'm fine.
Damai is more serious.
Luckily I finished the 3,000 words
yesterday before I had an attack.
Is writing more important than life?
As long as I live,
I have to update.
Why am I so tired?
I can't eat anymore.
Eat first.
Okay.
I'm really hungry.
This stovetop shed roof
needs to be repaired.
The soil is falling down.
Wait until we harvest the plums.
When eating, look carefully...
Our agreement.
Good food.
Funny things.
The people I love.
Let it be.
What does this mean?
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
[Hei is super cold.]
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
[The people I love. Let it be.]
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫
I don't want to let you go.
Time goes by too fast.
It doesn't matter.
I often go to Changsha on business.
When I go, you have
to treat me to good food.
No problem.
If you go,
I'll take care of all the things for you.
Okay.
When will you go back?
In half a month.
Time is so fast.
You don't want to leave, right?
Actually,
everyone is really nice to you.
I know.
And
the good that you don't know.
Help Damai?
Damai has recently
been considering giving up writing
and getting a job.
In fact, we can all tell that
she is very painful and very torn.
Because she still likes writing.
As her friend, I don't
want to stand by,
and want to give her a push.
What can I do?
Damai is usually very nerdy,
and her schedule is irregular.
Her day and night are reversed.
Especially when she can't write,
she is more likely to
keep herself in the room
in a bad mental state.
Here's what I think.
You two are both creators,
and you can talk together.
You can encourage her more.
At least, let her out
in the sun more often,
which is good for her health.
No problem.
I also have something
to ask Damai for help.
But she's so talented,
why would she give up?
Yes.
You think so too?
Actually, Damai's
writing is really good.
But those comments are so weird.
Like it's not sweet at all.
Suspense and mystery novel,
of course, it's not sweet.
Besides, someone blames that
the mistress had a
five-year relationship,
so disgusting.
I'm so angry.
Someone even denigrates the author.
They say the author must have
psychological problems.
Nonsense.
Don't care about such comments.
Anyway, Hongdou and I think
her writing is really good.
You must read it.
Must read it.
Okay.
Bt the way,
I... I have to ask
for Damai's consent
before sending her column link to you.
Let me ask her first.
It's okay. I'll just ask her.
Remember to tell
her that you really like
suspense and romance novels.
Okay.
Damai,
when you are in trouble,
don't hold on alone.
Sometimes, you can
also rely on friends.
Hongdou.
Hongdou,
are you up?
Wait.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Damai replied to me.
Let me read it to you.
I've read all your comments.
Your encouragement and support
are very important to me.
I will continue to write hard.
Love you and thank you.
So early in the morning,
I thought something was wrong.
She replied to you too.
And she replied to
all the other accounts I registered.
She hasn't read the
comments for a long time.
Now she's reading them again.
And she even updated more yesterday.
Your strategy is great.
From now on, we will be
the most loyal readers of Damai.
We should guard her together silently.
Damai.
Hello. Good morning.
Good morning.
I've been up all
night, and didn't sleep.
Did the writing go well?
I didn't write it out.
Why didn't you write it again?
Because the creation itself
is a combination of self-doubt, tears,
countless late nights
and the occasional flash of insight.
Exactly.
Hu,
have you written it?
Not at all.
Is he okay?
I'm the same as you.
Uncle Chang.
The Fifth Hospital, right?
Okay.
I'm... I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Aunt Feng, what's wrong?
My husband fainted.
I have to go home to
get his ID and money.
Where's my phone?
Here.
Aunt Feng, don't panic.
It may not be serious.
How did he faint?
I'm...
Arrogant.
I'm not here for you.
I'm here to Baoping.
Chuchu.
Aunt Gui, Uncle Chang fainted.
Aunt Feng was scared.
She went back alone,
can she handle it?
Fainted?
How could?
It's okay.
I'll go check it out.
This is for Baoping.
One is for Feng.
Okay.
Be careful.
Feng.
Get on.
Let me take you to the hospital.
I'm going to the Fifth Hospital.
My husband has fainted.
Hurry up.
I know.
Sit still.
Isn't this dangerous?
It's so scary.
Yao.
Aunt Feng, Aunt Gui.
How is my husband?
Uncle Chang is fine.
He's awake, and
in for an infusion.
Okay.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Yao,
your Uncle Chang has fainted.
What did the doctor say?
He is anemic due to malnutrition.
His hemoglobin is only 70 grams.
Is that serious?
Yes, a little serious.
Very serious.
If I hadn't passed
by and seen him,
he was lying there, it
would have been serious.
That's true.
Thanks to Second Bro.
Luckily.
Nothing.
Yao,
I'll leave now.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Don't worry.
You scared me.
Yao,
you stay here.
I'm going back too.
Don't you go in and take a look?
I don't take anything.
I'm too embarrassed to go in.
You stay, I'm leaving.
Where are Gui and Qin's father?
They go back.
Leave?
The doctor also said that
when Uncle Chang gets better,
take him to a big hospital in the city
to do a full body checkup.
Does he need blood supplements?
Yes.
Let me tell you.
Granny, step back a bit.
The spilled oil will burn you.
Turn it over.
Stir-fry green vegetables
with light soy sauce.
But you put dark soy sauce.
It's okay.
That's how we do it in my hometown.
The way you do it in your hometown.
Then put in less salt.
Okay.
Less.
Enough?
Add some more.
Okay.
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫